pngtree.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy of Pngtree

April 3, 2019

Pngtree attaches great importance to protecting users' information security and privacy. It protects your personal data for the purpose of Pngtree's pursuit of legitimate interests and your effective use of the Pngtree website. Pngtree has established the following privacy policies in accordance with current regulations and strictly adheres to protect users' data information and privacy.

By using and accessing our website, you admit that you have read this Privacy Policy and fully agree with it. The latest update contents to this Privacy Policy are at the top of this article and will be effective as soon as they are released. Therefore, Pngtree recommends timely reviewing this Privacy Policy.

Definition of Data

Data received from the Privacy Policy Adjustments, all "Personal Information" collected and maintained by Pngtree when you visit Pngtree, which is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person to whom such information belongs. 

The information does not include: 

1\. racial or ethnic origin; 

2\. political views; 

3\. religious/philosophical beliefs; 

4\. union membership; 

5\. data relating to health, sexual life or sexual orientation; 

6\. genetic data 

7\. Processed to identify biometric data for a specific individual. 

In order to take the necessary duty of care, pngtree may verify that you have admitted pngtree to collect content related to your personal photo, but the collection process will be subject to your express consent.

Legal Basis for Data Collection

Pngtree's privacy policy is guided by the EU General Data Protection Regulations and the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act. Pngtree's data collection and processing is mainly based on the following points:

(1) Your consent: You are authorized to collect and process your data. If you are a child under the age of 16, your consent should be sent by your legal representative or confirmed by the legal representative. Otherwise please stop using this website;

(2) In order to perform the contract with you, when data processing is required;

(3) Data processing is necessary to protect the data subject or other natural persons' important interests;

(4) Data processing will promote the legitimate interests of Pngtree;

(5) When the payment platform and the bank participate in the transaction, they must share the user data with the third-party payment institution in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations and ensure the smooth operation of the transaction;

(6) Data processing is a legal obligation that Pngtree must fulfill.

Activity Record of Data Collection

1\. Data Management and Control

Shanghai Huaitu Network Technology Co., Ltd. is the data controller and is responsible for collecting and processing on the pngtree website.

Company Address: Shanghai Pudong District Bibo Road No. 690, Building 1, Room 102

Email: info@pngtree.com

Contact Number: 0086021-61109163

We have assigned a data protection contact to Pngtree to review issues related to this privacy statement. If you have any questions or requests regarding this privacy statement, related issues regarding your data acquisition and processing, please contact the reservation information below.

Data Protection Contact: Data Protection Officer

Email: privacy@pngtree.com

Contact Number: 0086021-61109163

2\. Our Purpose and Legal Basis of Data we Collect

Data collection trigger

| 

Data content

| 

Our Purpose  
  
---|---|---  
  
Access or use the Pngtree website through a browser

| 

Technical data: your access traces, search, browsing, collection, download, website usage patterns, etc.

| 

To fulfill the contract and optimize our service experience  
  
Become a registered user of Pngtree

| 

User name and user ID, contact information (email or mobile phone number, third party associated identity content)

| 

Use and provision of services, some of which are legal obligations that Pngtree must fulfill  
  
Become a registered Premium Plan member of Pngtree

| 

Username and user ID, contact information (email or mobile number, third-party associated identity content), payment and billing data

| 

Use and provision of services, some of which are legal obligations that Pngtree must fulfill  
  
Request to consult or answer questions

| 

Your name, contact details, materials on which your complaint is based, and other information needed to answer your questions

| 

Answer inquiries, suggestions, events or claims  
  
Request to become partner of Pngtree

| 

If you become a partner of Pngtree or a contributor, we will also collect from you as necessary: your true identity and supporting materials, your contact details, your collection and settlement data, your recipient address, etc.

| 

Use and provide services to ensure that your interests are available and promote the legitimate interests of Pngtree  
  
3\. How do we collect?

(1) Browse and use this website:

Usually, when users browse our website anonymously, Pngtree does not require users to disclose any personal data.

But when users access and use our website, user behavior will trigger some tools/techniques to automatically store and collect information. This information is related to the technical information of the browsing activity and usage patterns. We collect this data by using cookies and similar technologies. Here are our instructions and rules for cookies and similar technologies: cookie and tracking technology.

Cookies are important to improve a user's web experience. Pngtree is generally used for the following purposes:

●    Verify identity

Cookies notify us when you access our services so that we can verify your identity to ensure your account is secure.

For example, Cookie technology notifies us when you visit Pngtree to identify if you are safely logged in and show you information about you.

●     Preferences 

Cookies help us to serve you according to the service style and appearance you wish.

For example, cookie technology can record whether you have read some suggestive presentations to prevent duplicate prompts from causing you harassment; some of your preferred settings (such as font size), we will also be stored in cookies, in your It will automatically adjust to the value you set last time when you visit.

●     Safety 

Cookies help us protect the security of our data and services, and detect cheating, hacking, and fraud (if any) for our products and services.

●     Features and services

Cookies help us provide better products and services to our users.

For example, cookies can help you fill in the name of the account you last logged in when you log in, through the stored information, to improve your operational efficiency.

●     Effectiveness 

Cookies can avoid unnecessary server load, improve service efficiency, and save resources and energy.

For example, cookies can help us optimize the flow of traffic between servers and understand the speed at which different users load our services. Sometimes we can use cookies to make you load and respond faster when you're using them.

●     Analysis and Research

We use these cookies to understand and improve our products and services, and to provide reference data for the development of new products or features.

For example, we use cookies to understand how you use our services in order to improve the user experience. For example, when you access our services, we collect this information at the time spent in each step to analyze aspects of the research that can be further optimized and improved.

●     Ad optimization (if any) 

Cookies increase the appeal of your ads to users and increase the value of your advertising services to advertisers and publishers. 

For example, cookies can help us show you ads that may be of interest to you on the Tencent website or in the software. We can also use cookies to know who saw the ad on Tencent's site and then browse the advertiser's website. Similarly, our partners may use cookies to determine whether we have displayed ads, understood the performance of our ads, or provided us with information about their interactions with you. 

How to manage cookies: 

Most browsers provide users with the ability to manage cookies. When the user is making a cookie setting in the browser, he can allow the website he trusts to enable the cookie function and prohibit other websites from using the cookie function.

For example, you can manage cookies in your Google Chrome settings. At the same time, you can also turn on the "Disable Tracking (DNT)" feature. However, please note that if you disable cookies, you may not be able to enjoy the best service experience and some services may not work properly.

(2) User registration, subscription to advanced services:

●     User registration 

When users register on our website, Pngtree stores data to develop websites, provide services (free or advanced) and provide certain features and options related to the service itself. We also use this data to send information, offers, promotions and news about services provided by Pngtree, sponsors or third parties, which provide services in the creative sector through newsletters or any other means of communication, including email. Product and phone number). Users can choose not to receive this information at any time via a user account or by sending an email to [info@pngtree.com].

●     Purchase membership service

Additional data such as name and payment and billing data (financial data) will be required so that we can process and execute the services requested by the user.

The payment and billing data depend on the payment method selected by the user and will be sent directly to the corresponding external payment service provider responsible for processing the payment.

(3) Request information about products, services or publications, and requests for website support services: 

Any information received by Pngtree will be stored in the Pngtree file and will only be used to respond to queries, suggestions or complaints sent by users of the website. This information includes data collected from contact forms, satisfaction surveys, and other information received through these two email addresses.

(4) Information provided through work and collaboration:

Any information provided to Pngtree by the "Work" and "Creation commission contract" forms available on the website will be stored in a file belonging to Pngtree and used solely to manage the internal recruitment process. In addition, if individuals enter our internal recruitment process to further accept their application, we will request and collect all necessary information required by the Labor and Tax Law of the People's Republic of China.

(5) Information provided when using the Google extension - Google Docs 

Users can browse and access certain Google apps anonymously, such as Google Docs. In this case, users only need to sign in with their Google Account and accept the Google Privacy Policy to find them here. 

Any information provided to the company as a result of using Google Docs will only be stored to ensure that the application is functioning properly. We may collect technical and statistical data by using cookies. For more information, please see our Cookie Policy. When using the Google app, we do not collect or store the personal data of the site users under any circumstances.

(6) Third-party website links 

Our website contains links to other websites whose privacy protection system may differ from Pngtree. If you submit personal information to any of these websites, your information will be governed by its privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

(7) Social media widgets

Our website may include social media features such as sharing and forwarding via a third-party platform that may collect your IP address, the pages you visit on our site, and may set a cookie to make this feature work. Social media features and widgets are hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature.

4\. Data protection

Pngtree will do its utmost to protect personal information obtained from users. To prevent users from being copied, modified, transmitted, lost or damaged under accidental or unauthorized access, pngtree will continue to take the following steps to protect your personal information:

1\. Encrypt the user's personal information in an appropriate manner;

2\. Use a password to protect the user's personal information in the appropriate location;

3\. Restrict access to personal information of users;

4\. Other reasonable measures.

Although reasonable and effective measures are taken in all cases and the relevant standards required by law and statutes must be observed, there is no guarantee that the security of your personal information will be fully protected. Therefore, users should take active measures to ensure the security of their personal information, such as periodically changing their account passwords, and not revealing personal information to others, such as their account passwords.

You know that the personal information protection provided by Pngtree is only available on the Pngtree platform. Once you leave Pngtree, the browser, or use other platforms, services or content resources, Pngtree has no ability and obligation to protect any personal information submitted on your Pngtree platform, whether you are logged in or browsing the above platforms based on Pngtree links or guides.

5\. The use of data

Pngtree collects your information to meet its legitimate business needs and the effective use of the website by users. We do not sell, rent or share your personally identifiable information to third parties in any other manner not disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

Pngtree may handle this information as follows:

(1) Verify and provide access to the Pngtree website.

(2) Customize your experience, including customizing our services, search results, and products for you.

(3) Handling your financial transactions.

(4) Send you an order/renewal confirmation.

(5) Respond to customer service requests, questions and concerns.

(6) Manage your account.

(7) Send the requested product or service information to you.

(8) Notify you of special offers and services from Pngtree and selected third parties.

(9) Manage the promotions and sweepstakes you participate in and inform you of the results.

(10) Investigate, prevent or take appropriate action against illegal activities and/or activities that violate the Terms of Service.

(11) Meet research and product/service development needs and improve our websites, services, and products.

(12) Register your rights (if any) with the Technical Support Department or other benefits available to registered users.

We store information collected through cookies, log files, transparent images, and/or third-party sources to create a summary of your preferences. We associate your personally identifiable information and/or member usage history with the information in the abstract to provide tailored promotional and marketing products and services, improve website content and/or determine your preferences.

In certain circumstances, Pngtree may be required to comply with legal obligations to disclose personal data in accordance with legal requests from public authorities. We may also investigate fraud cases when required by law (such as delivery of Pngtree's summons, warranties, court orders, or proceedings) and we believe it is necessary to disclose to protect our rights, avoid litigation, protect the safety of you or others, and investigate fraud. And disclose your information in response to government requests. In order to fulfill our legal obligations, we may also disclose your information if we determine that such disclosure is for national security, law enforcement or other publicly important matters.

6\. Your rights

Pngtree ensures that users can exercise the rights set forth in the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), which became applicable on May 25, 2018.

Users can exercise the following rights by sending an email.

Please note that Pngtree may require users to verify their identity before exercising their rights.

The user has the following rights:

1\. Access rights: The user has the right to obtain confirmation from Pngtree about whether or not the personal data related to it is being processed;

2\. Right of Correction: The user has the right to ask us to correct personal data if it is inaccurate or incorrect. When requesting correction, the user must indicate the data to be corrected and provide the correct information. In addition, requests must be sent with supplemental documents as necessary to supplement incomplete or inaccurate data.

3\. Erase rights: Users have the right to request the deletion of personal data about their personal accounts. When requesting to terminate an account and thus delete all personal information, the user must be aware of the following:

(1) Personal information may be retained and used as necessary to perform its legal obligations under financial obligations and associated with judicial information and auditing;

(2) If the user sends an erase request, the personal data will be deleted from Pngtree's secure backup system when the next backup is completed.

(3) Pngtree will not actively delete your personal data. As long as your account is valid, we will keep your information, verify or enforce the license to use the content if necessary, and retain the services you need to fulfill or fulfill our legal obligations. Information.

4\. Right of revocation: In the case that the user authorizes the processing of its data, the user has the right to withdraw his consent at any time. Revocation consent can be obtained by e-mail, and the user is asked to specify the consent that he wishes to revoke.

Please note that revoking consent does not affect the legality of the processing based on consent prior to revocation.

7\. Modify the privacy protection policy

Pngtree reserves the right to amend any terms of the Privacy Policy at any time.

Once the content of the privacy policy changes, Pngtree will announce its changes to the Privacy Policy on the Pngtree platform.

This posting is considered to be notified by Pngtree to modify the content. Pngtree can also prompt the user to modify the content in other appropriate ways.

If you do not agree to Pngtree's changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you have the right to stop using the Pngtree Service.

If you continue to use Pngtree's services, you will be deemed to have received Pngtree's changes to the terms of this Agreement.

8\. Submit complaints and data protection contacts

If you wish to raise any other objection to the processor's personal data, we hope that you can contact Pngtree directly or notify the data protection contact, please ask your request, objection, inquiry or suggestion regarding your personal privacy policy as detailed as possible. Description, this will help us solve problems for you more efficiently.

Our contact information: Data Protection Officer

The contact information of Email: privacy@pngtree.com

Telephone: 0086021-61109163
